{
  "uniqueId": "english definitions 18",
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "STRICT",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "characteristic of a baby",
      "answer": "babyish"
    },
    {
      "question": "discourage or frighten with threats or a domineering manner",
      "answer": "browbeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "oily egg-shaped nut of an American tree of the walnut family  ",
      "answer": "butternut"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or part of trees or shrubs bearing cones and evergreen leaves  ",
      "answer": "coniferous"
    },
    {
      "question": "farthest to the east  ",
      "answer": "easternmost"
    },
    {
      "question": "large black-and-white crested eagle of tropical America  ",
      "answer": "harpy"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an interesting manner",
      "answer": "interestingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a gloomy ill-tempered feeling  ",
      "answer": "moroseness"
    },
    {
      "question": "being ten more than eighty  ",
      "answer": "ninety"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or characterized by propaganda  ",
      "answer": "propagandist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a decorative wall bracket for holding candles or other sources of light  ",
      "answer": "sconce"
    },
    {
      "question": "(pathology) constriction of a body part so as to cut off the flow of blood or other fluid",
      "answer": "strangulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "not trimmed",
      "answer": "untrimmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being able to meet a need satisfactorily: \"he questioned the adequacy of the usual sentimental interpretation of the Golden Rule\"  ",
      "answer": "adequacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "having bones as specified",
      "answer": "boned"
    },
    {
      "question": "a perfumed liquid made of essential oils and alcohol  ",
      "answer": "cologne"
    },
    {
      "question": "the formation of stonelike objects within a body organ (e.g., the kidneys)  ",
      "answer": "concretion"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being melted and fused  ",
      "answer": "fusible"
    },
    {
      "question": "wading birds of warm regions having long slender down-curved bills  ",
      "answer": "ibis"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from duties or responsibilities",
      "answer": "leisured"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a parenthetical manner",
      "answer": "parenthetically"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to pugilism or pugilists",
      "answer": "pugilistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) an explanation of the fundamental reasons (especially an explanation of the working of some device in terms of laws of nature)",
      "answer": "rationale"
    },
    {
      "question": "susceptible to improvement or reform",
      "answer": "redeemable"
    },
    {
      "question": "the attribute of being restful",
      "answer": "restfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or involved in or characteristic of schism",
      "answer": "schismatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "without supper",
      "answer": "supperless"
    },
    {
      "question": "at a moderately slow tempo",
      "answer": "andante"
    },
    {
      "question": "essential oil or perfume obtained from flowers  ",
      "answer": "attar"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic or indicative of a disease",
      "answer": "diagnostic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 7th letter of the Greek alphabet  ",
      "answer": "eta"
    },
    {
      "question": "born free of free parents  ",
      "answer": "freeborn"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality possessed by something that is excessively expensive  ",
      "answer": "lavishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the inner part of an organ or structure in plant or animal  ",
      "answer": "medulla"
    },
    {
      "question": "young hen usually less than a year old  ",
      "answer": "pullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of pelting with stones",
      "answer": "stoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "a card game (usually for two players) in which each player is dealt six cards and discards one or two  ",
      "answer": "cribbage"
    },
    {
      "question": "the number by which a multiplicand is multiplied  ",
      "answer": "multiplier"
    },
    {
      "question": "a macintosh made from cotton fabric treated with oil and pigment to make it waterproof  ",
      "answer": "oilskin"
    },
    {
      "question": "not objectionable",
      "answer": "unobjectionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flat stone for sharpening edged tools or knives  ",
      "answer": "whetstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut small bits or pare shavings from",
      "answer": "whittle"
    },
    {
      "question": "triteness or triviality of style  ",
      "answer": "bathos"
    },
    {
      "question": "a milky fluid consisting of lymph and emulsified fats",
      "answer": "chyle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a rationale for dialectical materialism based on change through the conflict of opposing forces  ",
      "answer": "dialectics"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loose dressing gown for women  ",
      "answer": "negligee"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a palace  ",
      "answer": "palatine"
    },
    {
      "question": "fraught with danger",
      "answer": "parlous"
    },
    {
      "question": "any animal that feeds on refuse and other decaying organic matter  ",
      "answer": "scavenger"
    },
    {
      "question": "that is passing through",
      "answer": "transpiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "relieve oneself of troubling information  ",
      "answer": "unbosom"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an acceptable (but not outstanding) manner",
      "answer": "acceptably"
    },
    {
      "question": "the positively charged terminal of a voltaic cell or storage battery that supplies current  ",
      "answer": "cathode"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cigar with both ends cut flat  ",
      "answer": "cheroot"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of rural life",
      "answer": "countrified"
    },
    {
      "question": "the complete destruction of every trace of something  ",
      "answer": "eradication"
    },
    {
      "question": "an explanation or critical interpretation (especially of the Bible)  ",
      "answer": "exegesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "the season for cutting and drying and storing grass as fodder  ",
      "answer": "haying"
    },
    {
      "question": "a chemical compound containing the hydroxyl group  ",
      "answer": "hydroxide"
    },
    {
      "question": "offer as a sacrifice by killing or by giving up to destruction",
      "answer": "immolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of Christian theology devoted to the refutation of errors  ",
      "answer": "polemics"
    },
    {
      "question": "make conspicuous or noteworthy  ",
      "answer": "signalize"
    },
    {
      "question": "an edict of the Russian tsar  ",
      "answer": "ukase"
    },
    {
      "question": "not subject to guidance or control after launching",
      "answer": "unguided"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of operating on living animals (especially in scientific research)  ",
      "answer": "vivisection"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an eagerly voracious manner",
      "answer": "voraciously"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes and repairs wooden wheels  ",
      "answer": "wheelwright"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of instruments in the violin family) to be played with the bow  ",
      "answer": "arco"
    },
    {
      "question": "the hollow under the arm where it is joined to the shoulder",
      "answer": "armpit"
    },
    {
      "question": "burrowing rodent of the family Geomyidae having large external cheek pouches",
      "answer": "gopher"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of totally saturating something with a substance",
      "answer": "impregnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing one mole of a substance",
      "answer": "molar"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of nice  ",
      "answer": "niceness"
    },
    {
      "question": "an optical instrument that provides a view of an otherwise obstructed field  ",
      "answer": "periscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being pliant and flexible  ",
      "answer": "pliancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "not claimed or called for by an owner or assignee",
      "answer": "unclaimed"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes wine  ",
      "answer": "vintner"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling a tree in form and branching structure",
      "answer": "arboreal"
    },
    {
      "question": "an explosive bomb or artillery shell  ",
      "answer": "bombshell"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small tool or hooklike implement  ",
      "answer": "crotchet"
    },
    {
      "question": "denial of any connection with or knowledge of  ",
      "answer": "disavowal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the discontinuation of a franchise",
      "answer": "disfranchisement"
    },
    {
      "question": "an outer protective covering such as the skin of an animal or a cuticle or seed coat or rind or shell  ",
      "answer": "integument"
    },
    {
      "question": "fitted or decorated with panels or wainscoting  ",
      "answer": "paneled"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stout straight knife used in Malaysia and Indonesia  ",
      "answer": "parang"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or consisting of participles",
      "answer": "participial"
    },
    {
      "question": "participating in organized resistance to a constituted government",
      "answer": "rebellious"
    },
    {
      "question": "set to zero",
      "answer": "reset"
    },
    {
      "question": "political independence",
      "answer": "separateness"
    },
    {
      "question": "apt to speak irritably",
      "answer": "snappish"
    },
    {
      "question": "that has been violently compressed",
      "answer": "squashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dish made by folding a piece of pastry over a filling  ",
      "answer": "turnover"
    },
    {
      "question": "a period of time during which there is armed conflict  ",
      "answer": "wartime"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or functioning as an adverb",
      "answer": "adverbial"
    },
    {
      "question": "joined together into a whole",
      "answer": "amalgamate"
    },
    {
      "question": "striking in variety and interest",
      "answer": "colorful"
    },
    {
      "question": "affecting extreme elegance in dress and manner  ",
      "answer": "dandified"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who denies  ",
      "answer": "denier"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove the inner part or the core of",
      "answer": "excavate"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the activity or business for which you are trained",
      "answer": "occupational"
    },
    {
      "question": "deep serious thoughtfulness  ",
      "answer": "pensiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a presumptuous manner",
      "answer": "presumptuously"
    },
    {
      "question": "continually complaining or faultfinding",
      "answer": "shrewish"
    },
    {
      "question": "frighten or scare, and often provoke into a violent action",
      "answer": "spook"
    },
    {
      "question": "cat-like mammal typically secreting musk used in perfumes  ",
      "answer": "civet"
    },
    {
      "question": "having all sides or faces equal  ",
      "answer": "equilateral"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female giant  ",
      "answer": "giantess"
    },
    {
      "question": "commit to memory",
      "answer": "memorize"
    },
    {
      "question": "determination of the length of a curve",
      "answer": "rectification"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being senile  ",
      "answer": "senility"
    },
    {
      "question": "farthest to the west  ",
      "answer": "westernmost"
    },
    {
      "question": "a serviceman in the artillery  ",
      "answer": "artilleryman"
    },
    {
      "question": "beat somebody on the soles of the feet  ",
      "answer": "bastinado"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being defined, limited, or explained",
      "answer": "definable"
    },
    {
      "question": "have the connection undone",
      "answer": "disjoined"
    },
    {
      "question": "coarse curly-leafed cabbage  ",
      "answer": "kale"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the piquant burning taste of peppers",
      "answer": "peppery"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fabric with prominent rounded crosswise ribs  ",
      "answer": "rep"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large structure for open-air sports or entertainments  ",
      "answer": "stadium"
    },
    {
      "question": "a room or establishment where alcoholic drinks are served over a counter",
      "answer": "barroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "containing or imposing condemnation or censure",
      "answer": "condemnatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cart drawn by a dog  ",
      "answer": "dogcart"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of lengthening something  ",
      "answer": "elongation"
    },
    {
      "question": "skillfulness by virtue of possessing special knowledge  ",
      "answer": "expertness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a hypocritical manner",
      "answer": "hypocritically"
    },
    {
      "question": "extinct elephant-like mammal that flourished worldwide from Miocene through Pleistocene times",
      "answer": "mastodon"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ribbonlike strip of pasta  ",
      "answer": "noodle"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to telephony",
      "answer": "telephonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small machine that is used for mathematical calculations  ",
      "answer": "calculator"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct a spray of water into a bodily cavity, for cleaning  ",
      "answer": "douche"
    },
    {
      "question": "insert surreptitiously or without warrant  ",
      "answer": "foist"
    },
    {
      "question": "device that heats water or supplies warmth to a room  ",
      "answer": "heater"
    },
    {
      "question": "upright consisting of a vertical side member of a door or window frame  ",
      "answer": "jamb"
    },
    {
      "question": "tennis played with one person on each side  ",
      "answer": "singles"
    },
    {
      "question": "so as to allow the passage of light",
      "answer": "transparently"
    },
    {
      "question": "ancient Greek or Roman galley or warship having three tiers of oars on each side  ",
      "answer": "trireme"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a speech expressing leave-taking",
      "answer": "valedictory"
    },
    {
      "question": "abstaining from unlawful sexual intercourse  ",
      "answer": "chaste"
    },
    {
      "question": "a possible event or occurrence or result  ",
      "answer": "eventuality"
    },
    {
      "question": "having power to atone for or offered by way of expiation or propitiation",
      "answer": "expiatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a businessperson who transports goods abroad (for sale)  ",
      "answer": "exporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "preventing realization or attainment of a desire  ",
      "answer": "frustrating"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of implementing (providing a practical means for accomplishing something)",
      "answer": "implementation"
    },
    {
      "question": "propel in a high arc",
      "answer": "lob"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who attacks in search of booty  ",
      "answer": "marauder"
    },
    {
      "question": "a German nobleman ranking above a count (corresponding in rank to a British marquess)  ",
      "answer": "margrave"
    },
    {
      "question": "a preliminary sculpture in wax or clay from which a finished work can be copied  ",
      "answer": "modeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "acid or granitic glass formed by the rapid cooling of lava without crystallization",
      "answer": "obsidian"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing remorse  ",
      "answer": "penitently"
    },
    {
      "question": "under terms not final or fully worked out or agreed upon",
      "answer": "probationary"
    },
    {
      "question": "habitual uncleanliness  ",
      "answer": "slovenliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the chief source of beryllium",
      "answer": "beryl"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a playfully devilish manner",
      "answer": "devilishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who breeds and trains hawks and who follows the sport of falconry  ",
      "answer": "falconer"
    },
    {
      "question": "warn in advance or beforehand",
      "answer": "forewarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "a secret look  ",
      "answer": "peek"
    },
    {
      "question": "restore to a state of good condition or operation  ",
      "answer": "rehabilitate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being untamed and ferocious",
      "answer": "savageness"
    },
    {
      "question": "sleep inducing  ",
      "answer": "soporific"
    },
    {
      "question": "small slender gull having narrow wings and a forked tail  ",
      "answer": "tern"
    },
    {
      "question": "not caught or not caught within bounds",
      "answer": "uncompleted"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of adjusting or aligning the parts of a device in relation to each other  ",
      "answer": "alignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mild powdered seasoning made from dried pimientos  ",
      "answer": "paprika"
    },
    {
      "question": "a culture containing yeast or bacteria that is used to start the process of fermentation or souring in making butter or cheese or dough",
      "answer": "starter"
    },
    {
      "question": "of the same kind",
      "answer": "suchlike"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or based on a text",
      "answer": "textual"
    },
    {
      "question": "any usually predatory wild animal considered undesirable",
      "answer": "varmint"
    },
    {
      "question": "evidence that refutes conclusively  ",
      "answer": "confutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dish in the form of a scallop shell  ",
      "answer": "coquille"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the cranium which encloses the brain",
      "answer": "cranial"
    },
    {
      "question": "an open automobile having a front seat and a rumble seat  ",
      "answer": "roadster"
    },
    {
      "question": "Roman Catholic",
      "answer": "beatified"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shop where books are sold  ",
      "answer": "bookshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a chaste and virtuous manner",
      "answer": "chastely"
    },
    {
      "question": "a series of chirps  ",
      "answer": "chirrup"
    },
    {
      "question": "the driver and keeper of an elephant  ",
      "answer": "mahout"
    },
    {
      "question": "the science and technology of metals  ",
      "answer": "metallurgy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of having or giving polarity  ",
      "answer": "polarization"
    },
    {
      "question": "the speech act of revoking or annulling or making void  ",
      "answer": "cancellation"
    },
    {
      "question": "(American football) putting the ball in play by passing it (between the legs) to a back",
      "answer": "centering"
    },
    {
      "question": "surrounding like a crown (especially of the blood vessels surrounding the heart)",
      "answer": "coronary"
    },
    {
      "question": "a system of principles governing morality and acceptable conduct  ",
      "answer": "ethic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an open box attached to a long pole handle",
      "answer": "hod"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being incapable of mutation",
      "answer": "immutability"
    },
    {
      "question": "a standard or model or pattern regarded as typical",
      "answer": "norm"
    },
    {
      "question": "attribute human qualities to something",
      "answer": "personify"
    },
    {
      "question": "relatively small placental mammals having a single pair of constantly growing incisor teeth specialized for gnawing  ",
      "answer": "rodent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of representing something with a symbol  ",
      "answer": "symbolizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various edible North American web-footed turtles living in fresh or brackish water  ",
      "answer": "terrapin"
    },
    {
      "question": "caused by or designed to retain heat",
      "answer": "thermal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a conventional name for a bear used in tales following usage in the old epic `Reynard the Fox'  ",
      "answer": "bruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "a capacious bag or basket  ",
      "answer": "carryall"
    },
    {
      "question": "a British financial system in which a bank or a post office transfers money from one account to another when they receive authorization to do so  ",
      "answer": "giro"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the Roman calendar: the 15th of March or May or July or October or the 13th of any other month  ",
      "answer": "ides"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an impassive manner",
      "answer": "impassively"
    },
    {
      "question": "(biology) a single-celled microorganism (especially a flagellate protozoan)  ",
      "answer": "monad"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who recites from memory  ",
      "answer": "reciter"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a slavish manner",
      "answer": "slavishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a retail dealer in tobacco and tobacco-related articles  ",
      "answer": "tobacconist"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a brilliant pure blue to purplish blue color  ",
      "answer": "ultramarine"
    },
    {
      "question": "not diluted",
      "answer": "undiluted"
    },
    {
      "question": "in abstract terms  ",
      "answer": "abstractly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sharp sour taste  ",
      "answer": "acerbity"
    },
    {
      "question": "vigorously active",
      "answer": "acrobatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an implement for beating  ",
      "answer": "beater"
    },
    {
      "question": "made to seem smaller or less (especially in worth)",
      "answer": "belittled"
    },
    {
      "question": "declare unfit",
      "answer": "disqualify"
    },
    {
      "question": "a word or phrase conveying no independent meaning but added to fill out a sentence or metrical line  ",
      "answer": "expletive"
    },
    {
      "question": "(horseshoes) the successful throw of a horseshoe or quoit so as to encircle a stake or peg  ",
      "answer": "ringer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hospital for recuperation or for the treatment of chronic diseases  ",
      "answer": "sanatorium"
    },
    {
      "question": "rotary engine in which the kinetic energy of a moving fluid is converted into mechanical energy by causing a bladed rotor to rotate  ",
      "answer": "turbine"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to wine  ",
      "answer": "vinous"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vivid manner",
      "answer": "vividly"
    },
    {
      "question": "large watertight chamber used for construction under water  ",
      "answer": "caisson"
    },
    {
      "question": "oblong cream puff  ",
      "answer": "eclair"
    },
    {
      "question": "adhering to fixed types or methods",
      "answer": "hieratic"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being imperious and overbearing  ",
      "answer": "imperiousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the power of creative imagination  ",
      "answer": "inventiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "greet with a salaam  ",
      "answer": "salaam"
    },
    {
      "question": "not inclined to talk or give information or express opinions  ",
      "answer": "uncommunicative"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical composition for voices and orchestra based on a religious text  ",
      "answer": "cantata"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of the short curved hairs that grow from the edges of the eyelids  ",
      "answer": "eyelash"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a leaf shape",
      "answer": "ovate"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a playfully roguish manner",
      "answer": "roguishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "motion sickness experienced while traveling on water  ",
      "answer": "seasickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of several large sharp-toothed marine food and sport fishes of the family Lutjanidae of mainly tropical coastal waters  ",
      "answer": "snapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "during the same period of time",
      "answer": "contemporaneously"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking sight",
      "answer": "eyeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "spend frivolously and unwisely",
      "answer": "fritter"
    },
    {
      "question": "an archaic term for a parrot  ",
      "answer": "popinjay"
    },
    {
      "question": "the position of secretary  ",
      "answer": "secretaryship"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of divisions of time) determined by daily motion of the stars",
      "answer": "sidereal"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a trustful manner",
      "answer": "trustfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from admixture with noxious elements",
      "answer": "uncontaminated"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who argues noisily or angrily  ",
      "answer": "wrangler"
    },
    {
      "question": "the business of a broker",
      "answer": "brokerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "expend, as from a fund  ",
      "answer": "disburse"
    },
    {
      "question": "a natural talent",
      "answer": "flair"
    },
    {
      "question": "fasten by passing through a hole or around something  ",
      "answer": "reeve"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is starving (or being starved)  ",
      "answer": "starveling"
    },
    {
      "question": "chimney consisting of a metal pipe of large diameter that is used to connect a stove to a flue  ",
      "answer": "stovepipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "anticipate with dread or anxiety  ",
      "answer": "apprehend"
    },
    {
      "question": "a worker whose trade is binding books  ",
      "answer": "bookbinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of inactivity or disuse  ",
      "answer": "desuetude"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small chin beard trimmed to a point",
      "answer": "goatee"
    },
    {
      "question": "a camp defended by a circular formation of wagons  ",
      "answer": "laager"
    },
    {
      "question": "a medicinal liquid that is rubbed into the skin to relieve muscular stiffness and pain  ",
      "answer": "liniment"
    },
    {
      "question": "next to the last",
      "answer": "penultimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "exercising power or authority  ",
      "answer": "regnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "move along on a luge or toboggan  ",
      "answer": "toboggan"
    },
    {
      "question": "a portion of something (especially money)  ",
      "answer": "tranche"
    },
    {
      "question": "without complaining",
      "answer": "uncomplainingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unmerited manner",
      "answer": "undeservedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of an arrow) not equipped with feathers",
      "answer": "unfledged"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) the assignment of particular areas of a magnetic disk to particular data or instructions  ",
      "answer": "allocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "anterior portion of the brain consisting of two hemispheres",
      "answer": "cerebrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "mostly widely cultivated species of everlasting flowers having usually purple flowers",
      "answer": "immortelle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small dynamo with a secondary winding that produces a high voltage enabling a spark to jump between the poles of a spark plug in a gasoline engine  ",
      "answer": "magneto"
    },
    {
      "question": "without clothing",
      "answer": "nakedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause (a chemical compound, vapour, solution, magnetic material) to unite with the greatest possible amount of another substance  ",
      "answer": "saturate"
    },
    {
      "question": "join by interweaving strands",
      "answer": "splice"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or involved in therapy",
      "answer": "therapeutic"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a trim manner",
      "answer": "trimly"
    },
    {
      "question": "not established by conditioning or learning",
      "answer": "unconditioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "preventing movement",
      "answer": "clogging"
    },
    {
      "question": "being or characterized by concepts or their formation",
      "answer": "conceptual"
    },
    {
      "question": "including markedly dissimilar elements",
      "answer": "disparate"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of genes) producing the same phenotype whether its allele is identical or dissimilar  ",
      "answer": "dominant"
    },
    {
      "question": "(genetics) the process of locating genes on a chromosome  ",
      "answer": "mapping"
    },
    {
      "question": "not marked by the use of reason",
      "answer": "mindless"
    },
    {
      "question": "combined with or having undergone a chemical reaction with oxygen",
      "answer": "oxidized"
    },
    {
      "question": "a white waxy substance from oil of the sperm whale  ",
      "answer": "spermaceti"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or connected with spiritualism  ",
      "answer": "spiritualistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who holds shares of stock in a corporation  ",
      "answer": "stockholder"
    },
    {
      "question": "an enveloping bandage  ",
      "answer": "swathe"
    },
    {
      "question": "pouring in abundance",
      "answer": "torrential"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of pouring a liquid from one vessel to another  ",
      "answer": "transfusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of reproduction) characterized by asexual processes  ",
      "answer": "vegetal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the rate at which energy is drawn from a source that produces a flow of electricity in a circuit",
      "answer": "voltage"
    },
    {
      "question": "breathe with difficulty  ",
      "answer": "wheeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or producing insensibility  ",
      "answer": "anaesthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "overturn accidentally",
      "answer": "capsize"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bottle with a stopper",
      "answer": "carafe"
    },
    {
      "question": "a uniformed doorman  ",
      "answer": "commissionaire"
    },
    {
      "question": "readily communicated",
      "answer": "communicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or resembling a cone",
      "answer": "conic"
    },
    {
      "question": "curl tightly",
      "answer": "crimp"
    },
    {
      "question": "confuse or put into disorder",
      "answer": "demoralize"
    },
    {
      "question": "dessert made by baking fruit wrapped in pastry  ",
      "answer": "dumpling"
    },
    {
      "question": "purified resinous extract of the hemp plant",
      "answer": "hashish"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that exists only as an idea  ",
      "answer": "idealization"
    },
    {
      "question": "(baseball) one of nine divisions of play during which each team has a turn at bat  ",
      "answer": "inning"
    },
    {
      "question": "very small European freshwater fish common in gravelly streams  ",
      "answer": "minnow"
    },
    {
      "question": "resembling the smell of musk  ",
      "answer": "musky"
    },
    {
      "question": "leaves of the common basil",
      "answer": "basil"
    },
    {
      "question": "(biology) a scientist who studies living organisms  ",
      "answer": "biologist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a nonmetallic heavy volatile corrosive dark brown liquid element belonging to the halogens",
      "answer": "bromine"
    },
    {
      "question": "occupy a trench or secured area",
      "answer": "entrench"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inoffensive or indirect expression that is substituted for one that is considered offensive or too harsh  ",
      "answer": "euphemism"
    },
    {
      "question": "a company emblem or device  ",
      "answer": "logo"
    },
    {
      "question": "extending throughout an entire nation",
      "answer": "nationally"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who has general authority over others  ",
      "answer": "overlord"
    },
    {
      "question": "chiefly nocturnal predacious arthropod having a flattened body of 15 to 173 segments each with a pair of legs, the foremost pair being modified as prehensors  ",
      "answer": "centipede"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a narrow-minded dogmatic manner",
      "answer": "dogmatically"
    },
    {
      "question": "taken for your own use in violation of a trust",
      "answer": "embezzled"
    },
    {
      "question": "the performance of a juggler  ",
      "answer": "jugglery"
    },
    {
      "question": "hating mankind in general  ",
      "answer": "misanthropic"
    },
    {
      "question": "election again",
      "answer": "reelection"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with shellac",
      "answer": "shellac"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small ornamental box for carrying snuff in your pocket  ",
      "answer": "snuffbox"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mischievous supernatural being found in the folklore of many primitive people",
      "answer": "trickster"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to chronology",
      "answer": "chronologically"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being hardened by some additive or other agent  ",
      "answer": "curable"
    },
    {
      "question": "without taking pains",
      "answer": "cursorily"
    },
    {
      "question": "take away the enthusiasm of  ",
      "answer": "dishearten"
    },
    {
      "question": "bearing or containing fossils",
      "answer": "fossiliferous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a green or blue mineral used as an ore of copper and for making ornamental objects  ",
      "answer": "malachite"
    },
    {
      "question": "an insect in the inactive stage of development (when it is not feeding) intermediate between larva and adult  ",
      "answer": "pupa"
    },
    {
      "question": "by indirect means",
      "answer": "secondhand"
    },
    {
      "question": "artificial as if portrayed in a film",
      "answer": "celluloid"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerned with or producing electric current  ",
      "answer": "electromotive"
    },
    {
      "question": "intermediate between peat and bituminous coal  ",
      "answer": "lignite"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various Old World tropical palmlike trees having huge prop roots and edible conelike fruits and leaves like pineapple leaves  ",
      "answer": "pandanus"
    },
    {
      "question": "a vote by the electorate determining public opinion on a question of national importance  ",
      "answer": "plebiscite"
    },
    {
      "question": "hand tool consisting of a stick with a rubber suction cup at one end",
      "answer": "plunger"
    },
    {
      "question": "the remains of a body part that was functional at an earlier stage of life",
      "answer": "rudiment"
    },
    {
      "question": "behavior marked by a bold defiance of the proprieties and lack of shame  ",
      "answer": "shamelessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a superstitious manner",
      "answer": "superstitiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "not desired",
      "answer": "undesired"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsuitable or forbidden as a topic of conversation",
      "answer": "unmentionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a workman who wets the work in a manufacturing process  ",
      "answer": "wetter"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or characteristic of Impressionism",
      "answer": "impressionist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is very small but who is not otherwise deformed or abnormal  ",
      "answer": "manikin"
    },
    {
      "question": "devotion to the interests or culture of a particular nation including promoting the interests of one country over those of others",
      "answer": "nationalist"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of persons) pleasant in appearance and personality  ",
      "answer": "personable"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being renewed",
      "answer": "renewable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a soldier whose weapon is a rifle  ",
      "answer": "rifleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "a roll of coins wrapped in paper  ",
      "answer": "rouleau"
    },
    {
      "question": "destitute of sap and other vital juices",
      "answer": "sapless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a set of three literary or dramatic works related in subject or theme  ",
      "answer": "trilogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "not in an official capacity",
      "answer": "unofficially"
    },
    {
      "question": "a chapel endowed for singing Masses for the soul of the donor  ",
      "answer": "chantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short line of text that a web site puts on your computer's hard drive when you access the web site  ",
      "answer": "cookie"
    },
    {
      "question": "being of coordinate importance, rank, or degree  ",
      "answer": "coordination"
    },
    {
      "question": "in fancy clothing  ",
      "answer": "dressy"
    },
    {
      "question": "an appraisal of the value of something",
      "answer": "evaluation"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an indecent manner",
      "answer": "indecently"
    },
    {
      "question": "having only one spouse at a time  ",
      "answer": "monogamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of pages) worn or soiled by thumb and fingers by frequent handling or turning",
      "answer": "thumbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a deficiency of moisture (especially when resulting from a permanent absence of rainfall)  ",
      "answer": "aridity"
    },
    {
      "question": "tastelessly showy",
      "answer": "brassy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the news as presented by reporters for newspapers or radio or television",
      "answer": "coverage"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unpolished unrefined quality",
      "answer": "crudeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an impious manner",
      "answer": "impiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "the upper part of a glacier (beyond the limit of perpetual snow) where the snow turns to ice  ",
      "answer": "neve"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or related to or derived from oats",
      "answer": "oaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a military force who is residing in a conquered foreign country  ",
      "answer": "occupier"
    },
    {
      "question": "pastors collectively  ",
      "answer": "pastorate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shallow metal bowl (usually with a handle)",
      "answer": "porringer"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepared or converted from a natural state by subjecting to a special process",
      "answer": "processed"
    },
    {
      "question": "fisherman's lure",
      "answer": "spinner"
    },
    {
      "question": "state of being disconnected  ",
      "answer": "disjunction"
    },
    {
      "question": "(chemistry) the temporary or reversible process in which a molecule or ion is broken down into smaller molecules or ions  ",
      "answer": "dissociation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flavored sugar topping used to coat and decorate cakes  ",
      "answer": "frosting"
    },
    {
      "question": "a monosaccharide sugar that has several forms",
      "answer": "glucose"
    },
    {
      "question": "revealing lack of perceptiveness or judgment or finesse",
      "answer": "inept"
    },
    {
      "question": "a warmness resembling the temperature of the skin  ",
      "answer": "lukewarmness"
    },
    {
      "question": "without scruples",
      "answer": "unscrupulously"
    },
    {
      "question": "the party who appeals a decision of a lower court  ",
      "answer": "appellant"
    },
    {
      "question": "a colorless liquid hydrocarbon",
      "answer": "benzene"
    },
    {
      "question": "very hard tough close-grained light yellow wood of the box (particularly the common box)",
      "answer": "boxwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "leaves used sparingly in soups and stews  ",
      "answer": "caraway"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being moderately cold",
      "answer": "chilliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold (a person or thing) close, as for affection, comfort, or warmth",
      "answer": "cuddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "expel intestinal gases through the anus  ",
      "answer": "fart"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being luminous",
      "answer": "luminosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "traffic in ecclesiastical offices or preferments  ",
      "answer": "simony"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) an increase in a beneficiary's share in an estate (as when a co-beneficiary dies or fails to meet some condition or rejects the inheritance)  ",
      "answer": "accretion"
    },
    {
      "question": "caught as if in a mesh",
      "answer": "enmeshed"
    },
    {
      "question": "teaching or impressing upon the mind by frequent instruction or repetition  ",
      "answer": "inculcation"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or located in the region of the neck or throat",
      "answer": "jugular"
    },
    {
      "question": "shaped like a boat  ",
      "answer": "navicular"
    },
    {
      "question": "fit for a sea voyage  ",
      "answer": "seaworthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "with laces not tied",
      "answer": "unlaced"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to diminish or disparage",
      "answer": "belittling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a checkerboard used to play chess  ",
      "answer": "chessboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a clucking sounds, characteristic of hens  ",
      "answer": "cluck"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small globe or ball  ",
      "answer": "globule"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of behaving in ways considered typical for men  ",
      "answer": "masculinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "beaver-like aquatic rodent of North America with dark glossy brown fur  ",
      "answer": "muskrat"
    },
    {
      "question": "not plowed or harrowed or hoed",
      "answer": "untilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "(in India) a native nursemaid who looks after children  ",
      "answer": "ayah"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard outer covering or case of certain organisms such as arthropods and turtles  ",
      "answer": "carapace"
    },
    {
      "question": "a movement in literature and art during the 17th and 18th centuries in Europe that favored rationality and restraint and strict forms",
      "answer": "classicism"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of determining that something is false  ",
      "answer": "falsification"
    },
    {
      "question": "a light plain-weave or twill-weave silk or silklike fabric (usually with a printed design)  ",
      "answer": "foulard"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) any computer that is hooked up to a computer network  ",
      "answer": "node"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to be off balance",
      "answer": "overbalance"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fashion reminiscent of the past  ",
      "answer": "retro"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who owns a ship or a share in a ship  ",
      "answer": "shipowner"
    },
    {
      "question": "a merchant who sells writing materials and office supplies  ",
      "answer": "stationer"
    },
    {
      "question": "up to that time",
      "answer": "theretofore"
    },
    {
      "question": "male sheep especially a castrated one  ",
      "answer": "wether"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of collecting in a mass",
      "answer": "agglomeration"
    },
    {
      "question": "a man's testicles (from Cockney rhyming slang: cobbler's awl rhymes with ball)  ",
      "answer": "cobblers"
    },
    {
      "question": "medical specialist whose competence has been certified by a diploma granted by an appropriate professional group  ",
      "answer": "diplomate"
    },
    {
      "question": "show one's unhappiness or critical attitude",
      "answer": "grouch"
    },
    {
      "question": "unholiness by virtue of being profane  ",
      "answer": "profaneness"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to ablate",
      "answer": "ablative"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a capacity for adaptation",
      "answer": "adaptive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small explosive bomb thrown by hand or fired from a missile  ",
      "answer": "grenade"
    },
    {
      "question": "a military facility that serves as the headquarters for military police and in which military prisoners can be detained  ",
      "answer": "guardhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mental or personality disturbance not attributable to any known neurological or organic dysfunction  ",
      "answer": "neurosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "the principal character in a work of fiction  ",
      "answer": "protagonist"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat, process, heat, melt, or refine in a reverberatory furnace",
      "answer": "reverberate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a narrow elongated opening or fissure between two symmetrical parts  ",
      "answer": "rima"
    },
    {
      "question": "change key",
      "answer": "transpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being untidy and messy  ",
      "answer": "untidiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "exist together  ",
      "answer": "coexist"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is a detective  ",
      "answer": "dick"
    },
    {
      "question": "half the width of an em  ",
      "answer": "en"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inhabitant of an island  ",
      "answer": "islander"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time of life between 90 and 100  ",
      "answer": "nineties"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or pertaining to or of the nature of peat  ",
      "answer": "peaty"
    },
    {
      "question": "spoken as if with a thick tongue",
      "answer": "slurred"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of stone especially) not given a finished form by or as if by hewing",
      "answer": "unhewn"
    },
    {
      "question": "a grouping of words in a sentence  ",
      "answer": "collocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or provided in a domicile",
      "answer": "domiciliary"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small ring-shaped friedcake  ",
      "answer": "doughnut"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a fastidious manner",
      "answer": "fastidiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "exacting especially about details",
      "answer": "finical"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a wedding or marriage",
      "answer": "hymeneal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a whip with a lash of leather thongs twisted with wire",
      "answer": "knout"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lamp consisting of a flame directed at a cylinder of lime with a lens to concentrate the light",
      "answer": "limelight"
    },
    {
      "question": "consisting of or having the character of loam",
      "answer": "loamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bend or curve, as in a stream or river  ",
      "answer": "meander"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the medulla of any body part  ",
      "answer": "medullary"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of singing psalms or hymns  ",
      "answer": "psalmody"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is skilled at planning tactics  ",
      "answer": "tactician"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various elongated tactile or prehensile flexible organs that occur on the head or near the mouth in many animals",
      "answer": "tentacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a list of matters to be taken up (as at a meeting)  ",
      "answer": "agenda"
    },
    {
      "question": "carbonated drink flavored with extract from kola nuts (`dope' is a southernism in the United States)  ",
      "answer": "cola"
    },
    {
      "question": "a yard outside the front or rear door of a house  ",
      "answer": "dooryard"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fancy dock for small yachts and cabin cruisers  ",
      "answer": "marina"
    },
    {
      "question": "geniality, as through the effects of alcohol or marijuana  ",
      "answer": "mellowness"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a leaf shape) featherlike",
      "answer": "pinnate"
    },
    {
      "question": "morally degraded",
      "answer": "seamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "campaigning for something by making political speeches (stump speeches)  ",
      "answer": "stumping"
    },
    {
      "question": "without someone's knowledge",
      "answer": "unbeknown"
    },
    {
      "question": "a glass that has a stem and in which wine is served  ",
      "answer": "wineglass"
    },
    {
      "question": "without a saddle",
      "answer": "bareback"
    },
    {
      "question": "serving an aesthetic purpose in beautifying the body",
      "answer": "cosmetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "compulsory force or threat",
      "answer": "duress"
    },
    {
      "question": "exceedingly",
      "answer": "fabulously"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a frugal manner",
      "answer": "frugally"
    },
    {
      "question": "not having legs",
      "answer": "legless"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the function or responsibility or activity of management  ",
      "answer": "managerial"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a proud and unbroken spirit  ",
      "answer": "mettlesome"
    },
    {
      "question": "a workman employed to pack things into containers  ",
      "answer": "packer"
    },
    {
      "question": "quality of being lively and confident",
      "answer": "pertness"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone whose business is advertising  ",
      "answer": "advertiser"
    },
    {
      "question": "being characteristic of a boy  ",
      "answer": "boyishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the cords used to suspend a hammock  ",
      "answer": "clews"
    },
    {
      "question": "wild and menacing",
      "answer": "feral"
    },
    {
      "question": "established or prearranged unalterably",
      "answer": "foreordained"
    },
    {
      "question": "used as a lubricant and as a moderator in nuclear reactors  ",
      "answer": "graphite"
    },
    {
      "question": "without showing consistency",
      "answer": "inconsistently"
    },
    {
      "question": "extreme depression characterized by tearful sadness and irrational fears  ",
      "answer": "melancholia"
    },
    {
      "question": "device for converting sound waves into electrical energy  ",
      "answer": "microphone"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard or painful trouble or struggle",
      "answer": "throe"
    },
    {
      "question": "not capable of being put into another form or style or language",
      "answer": "untranslatable"
    },
    {
      "question": "the collective body of bishops  ",
      "answer": "episcopacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the murder of your sibling  ",
      "answer": "fratricide"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mound of fatty tissue covering the pubic area in women  ",
      "answer": "mons"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a patriotic manner",
      "answer": "patriotically"
    },
    {
      "question": "sexually unattractive  ",
      "answer": "sexless"
    },
    {
      "question": "spot, splash, or soil",
      "answer": "spatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a subjective way",
      "answer": "subjectively"
    },
    {
      "question": "a beam made usually of steel",
      "answer": "girder"
    },
    {
      "question": "the study of musical sound  ",
      "answer": "harmonics"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a levelheaded manner",
      "answer": "healthily"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ancient (now obsolete) single-reed woodwind",
      "answer": "hornpipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an irreparable manner or to an irreparable degree  ",
      "answer": "irreparably"
    },
    {
      "question": "adopting a vain conceited posture  ",
      "answer": "posturing"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or having the nature of retribution",
      "answer": "retaliatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "cheerfully irresponsible",
      "answer": "carefree"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of biology that studies the formation and early development of living organisms  ",
      "answer": "embryology"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long narrow inlet of the sea between steep cliffs",
      "answer": "fjord"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who writes radio or tv advertisements  ",
      "answer": "huckster"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of gloomy sorrow  ",
      "answer": "mournfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a document or receipt certifying release from an obligation or debt  ",
      "answer": "quittance"
    },
    {
      "question": "lower oneself with a rope coiled around the body from a mountainside",
      "answer": "rappel"
    },
    {
      "question": "logical and methodical reasoning  ",
      "answer": "ratiocination"
    },
    {
      "question": "right-hand page  ",
      "answer": "recto"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a stony manner",
      "answer": "stonily"
    },
    {
      "question": "worthy of a good workman",
      "answer": "workmanlike"
    },
    {
      "question": "shaped like a star  ",
      "answer": "asteroid"
    },
    {
      "question": "the transparent dome-shaped anterior portion of the outer covering of the eye",
      "answer": "cornea"
    },
    {
      "question": "a transverse and totally enclosed drain under a road or railway  ",
      "answer": "culvert"
    },
    {
      "question": "negotiate the terms of an exchange",
      "answer": "dicker"
    },
    {
      "question": "lose a stored charge, magnetic flux, or current",
      "answer": "disintegrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or containing an electrolyte  ",
      "answer": "electrolytic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a prior appropriation of something",
      "answer": "preemption"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no parts resembling rays",
      "answer": "rayless"
    },
    {
      "question": "altered or revised by rephrasing or by adding or deleting material",
      "answer": "revised"
    },
    {
      "question": "somewhat round in appearance or form  ",
      "answer": "roundish"
    },
    {
      "question": "an advocate of secession or separation from a larger group (such as an established church or a national union)  ",
      "answer": "separatist"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or according to or affecting a symptom or symptoms",
      "answer": "symptomatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "without regulation or discipline",
      "answer": "unregulated"
    },
    {
      "question": "a congenial disposition  ",
      "answer": "congeniality"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to explode violently and with loud noise  ",
      "answer": "fulminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a jovial manner",
      "answer": "jovially"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in Estonia  ",
      "answer": "kroon"
    },
    {
      "question": "mentally sluggish  ",
      "answer": "lumpish"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Roman Catholic Church) a greeting signifying Christian love for those assisting at the Eucharist  ",
      "answer": "pax"
    },
    {
      "question": "grant remission of a sin to",
      "answer": "shrive"
    },
    {
      "question": "support with a splint",
      "answer": "splint"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tasteful way",
      "answer": "aesthetically"
    },
    {
      "question": "at the present or from now on",
      "answer": "anymore"
    },
    {
      "question": "slender bristlelike appendage found on the bracts of grasses  ",
      "answer": "awn"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who meddles in the affairs of others  ",
      "answer": "busybody"
    },
    {
      "question": "dressed in clothing characteristic of a period, country, or class  ",
      "answer": "costumed"
    },
    {
      "question": "mental deterioration of organic or functional origin  ",
      "answer": "dementia"
    },
    {
      "question": "your deepest feelings of love and compassion",
      "answer": "heartstrings"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhaustion resulting from lack of food  ",
      "answer": "inanition"
    },
    {
      "question": "enter drop by drop",
      "answer": "instill"
    },
    {
      "question": "a slide of a large mass of dirt and rock down a mountain or cliff  ",
      "answer": "landslide"
    },
    {
      "question": "not shod  ",
      "answer": "unshod"
    }
  ]
}